♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪ فقط أريد أن أقول مرحبًا ♪
♪Hello♪
♪ مرحبا ♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
♪ أنت لا يمكن إيقافك ♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2= =Episode 33=
= Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2 = = الحلقة 33 =
Ms. Fu.
السيدة فو.
You said you will invest in our business
قلت أنك ستستثمر في أعمالنا
after we meet your dad, didn't you?
بعد أن قابلنا والدك ، أليس كذلك؟
Yeah. You have to keep your own words, right?
نعم.  عليك أن تحتفظ بكلماتك الخاصة ، أليس كذلك؟
Liars.
كذابون.
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Get out.
اخرج.
Or I'll call the police.
أو سأتصل بالشرطة.
But you promised us.
لكنك وعدتنا.
Why are you doing this?
لماذا تفعل هذا؟
Throw them out.
ارميهم للخارج.
Yes.
نعم.
Why do you do this?
لماذا تفعلون هذا؟
You promised us!
لقد وعدتنا!
Don't touch my mom!
لا تلمس أمي!
Ms. Fu!
السيدة فو!
I see!
أرى!
You want to take my patent as your own!
تريد أن تأخذ براءات الاختراع الخاصة بي على أنها ملكك!
Come back here!
عد إلى هنا!
What's wrong, Xiangxiang?
ما بك شيانغشيانغ؟
I'm okay.
أنا بخير.
Didn't you say you'll bring Fu Sihan
ألم تقل أنك ستحضر فو سيهان
to see me?
لرؤيتي؟
He...
هو...
He's busy lately.
إنه مشغول مؤخرًا.
So,
لذا،
he doesn't have the time.
ليس لديه الوقت.
He didn't...
لم يفعل ...
He didn't bully you, did he?
لم يتنمر عليك ، أليس كذلك؟
No. I'm fine, mom.
لا ، أنا بخير يا أمي.
Don't lie to me.
لا تكذب علي.
Look at you.
انظر لحالك.
No woman in love
لا امرأة في الحب
would look like that.
سيبدو هكذا.
I have a friend.
لدي صديق.
She's having some trouble
إنها تواجه بعض المشاكل
with her relationship.
مع علاقتها.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
You...
أنت...
Your friend.
صديقك.
What kind of trouble is she in?
في أي نوع من المشاكل هي؟
She has someone
لديها شخص ما
that she loves
التي تحبها
very much.
كثيرا جدا.
But for some reasons,
لكن لبعض الأسباب ،
they can't be together.
لا يمكن أن يكونوا معًا.
They are like the bird and the fish.
إنهم مثل الطائر والأسماك.
Even though they love each other,
على الرغم من أنهم يحبون بعضهم البعض ،
they can't be together
لا يمكن أن يكونوا معًا
for their whole life.
طوال حياتهم.
What's the big deal about it?
ما هي المشكلة الكبيرة في ذلك؟
Think about all those TV shows,
فكر في كل تلك البرامج التلفزيونية ،
My Love from the Star,
حبي من النجم
Ghost,
شبح،
and Descendants of the Sun.
وأحفاد الشمس.
The boys and girls in them,
الفتيان والفتيات فيها ،
they've gone through so much trouble and even risked their lives
لقد مروا بالكثير من المتاعب وخاطروا بحياتهم
just to be together.
فقط لنكون معا.
And in the end, they all live happily ever after.
وفي النهاية ، يعيشون جميعًا في سعادة دائمة.
A happy ending.
نهاية سعيدة.
But you know those are all TV dramas.
لكنك تعلم أن هذه كلها مسلسلات تلفزيونية.
It's not reality.
إنها ليست حقيقة.
You don't always get a happy ending in reality.
لا تحصل دائمًا على نهاية سعيدة في الواقع.
Xiangxiang.
شيانغشيانغ.
Mom knows
أمي تعرف
that life is short.
أن الحياة قصيرة.
If you meet the right one,
إذا قابلت الشخص المناسب ،
you have to overcome all the trouble
عليك أن تتغلب على كل المشاكل
with courage.
بشجاعة.
Don't regret it
لا تندم
after you've lost it.
بعد أن فقدتها.
Xiangxiang.
شيانغشيانغ.